(Penny:)Howard, I've asked you not to do that.
Leslie and I do research together
at the university.
(Penny:)Oh, wow. A girl scientist.
(Lesley:)Yep. Come for the breasts,
stay for the brains.
(Lesley:)So I'm glad I ran into you.
(Lesley:)The Physics Department string quartet
needs a new cellist.
What happened to Elliott Wong?
Switched over to high-energy
radiation research, had a mishap.
(Lesley:)And now the other guys
are uncomfortable sitting next to him.
(Lesley:)- So are you in?
- Yeah, sure. Why not?
(Lesley:)- We rehearse on Tuesdays at your place.
- Why at my place?
Yeah, Department of Energy said
our regular space is kind of a hot zone.
(Lesley:)- Nice meeting you.
- Yeah, you too.
(Penny:)Leonard, I didn't know
you played the cello.
(Leonard:)Yeah, my parents felt
that naming me Leonard...
(Leonard:)...and putting me
in advanced-placement classes...
(Leonard:)...wasn't getting me beaten up enough.
(Howard:)If you're into music, I happen
to be a human beatbox...
(Howard:)- ...so...
- Really?
[BEATBOXING]
(Penny:)I'm actually not that into music.